Hi guys, In this video, we are going to bring a new feature in Hicksfield.
So we are going to discuss about that feature in the end to end.
How it is and what we can use it.
So what is it?
It is called Kling 3.0.
It is a new model.
It has been integrated in this Hicksfield tool.
So in this video generation, it has a huge impact.
I will explain it clearly in this video.
This will have a huge impact on the next cinema.
There are many short films or films.
Many films are used by A.
You would have noticed that.
In that, I will explain how much this tool is going to play a major role.
If you want to learn more related content like this,
Follow our page without forgetting.
I have given the details, blocks and links in the description.
Check it without forgetting.
Now let's explore the feature completely.
So first, we are going to integrate the Kling 3.0 model.
It is not coming yet.
So what is the best feature?
First, you have the enhanced audio generation.
What is the difference between this and the previous one?
The audio quality of the video is less compared to the video.
Now, they have increased the Kling 3.0 version.
You can't find the difference between the video and the audio.
So the quality will be completely different.
If you are going to take a short film,
The cinema is very important.
If you take a short film, you won't take it from the same style.
We have to shoot a multi-shot film.
Then we can take the audience.
They have brought the Kling 3.0 feature.
It is called multi-shot narrative.
As you can see on the screen,
One of the people is running in the video with the rights.
But we capture it from a different angle.
So this is called multi-shot.
You can only achieve this shot through the prompt.
The Kling 3.0 feature is very helpful.
Next, there is the directoral physics.
It is very important.
They will tell you the unique shot.
We will see a lot in the cinema.
We will see a lot in the short films.
In this, you can capture a car in the mirror.
This is called directoral physics.
You can achieve this feature through the prompt.
That is the main thing.
The Kling 3.0 update is called motion control.
You can control the motion and produce a movie.
You can use this feature.
Next, native Aave now has a 4K cinematic workflow.
When you focus on one thing, the background is blurred.
It is portrayed.
You can notice the difference from one place to another.
This is actually our shoot.
But look at the evolution.
We are giving a prompt.
It is a great option.
I will definitely tell you that this has a big impact on the cinema industry.
You can take a movie with a camera that is 10 lakhs or 15 lakhs.
You can do the quality of the film through the prompt.
If you have an idea, you can do it through the prompt.
It has a big impact on the industry.
You can take many people with you.
This is a God level tool.
I am using this tool.
I am using it.
I am addicted to using it.
That is why I suggest you to apply A in your career.
You can use it for marketing.
You can leverage it and go to the next level.
You can also use this quality.
Extended cinematic facing.
You can also use it for the difference.
You can see the motion control.
You can achieve this by using the prompt.
The subject is the subject.
You can see the difference.
Extended is more than the previous one.
You can generate videos in extra seconds.
You can do it for nearly 15 seconds.
Let us see what other features are provided.
The main feature is that you have generated a video for 60 seconds.
You can do it in a single pixel.
You can create a new video or do it in a different way.
You can do it in a big orchestration.
You can do it in a video without a pixel.
This will help us a lot.
This is one of the best features.
If you do not get a video, you can generate it again.
You can do it in a target area.
I am seeing this in a big update.
This will help us to get a big impact.
You can see the intelligent scene.
You can see the generated video.
The couple is in a cave.
The details of the couple are clear.
The details are clear.
The couple is in a cave.
The clean 3.0 is an update.
You will get a clear understanding.
The clean 3.0 is a big update.
It is in the market.
I will give the link in the description.
Check it out.
I am waiting for this feature.
Comment below.
This is a visual communication tool.
This will help them to get a good experience.
This tool is a good experience.
You can leverage the tool to get a good experience.
The clean 3.0 is an update.
You can understand what is in the feature.
If you have learnt something like this from Corel AI,
Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Agent K
Subscribe to our channel.
See you in the next Tech related video.